My name is Daniel Hardman and I'm the CTO
of Provenant, which is a small startup in
the telco industry. My presentation was on
open verifiable calling. That acronym OVC
is changing into open verifiable
communication and it's all about proving
who is making some kind of a communication
flow to somebody else. So the big thing
that we're doing that I think is crucial
is we're providing evidence for the first
time about who is involved in
communication. Up until now, most efforts
to eliminate fraud have basically proved
somebody's opinion, but now we're actually
able to prove hard facts about the parties
involved. I think without the OVC
initiative, the entire telco industry is
missing an important insight and an
opportunity. Fraud is driving down the
usefulness of all of our communication
technologies and unless they come up with
an answer, people are going to stop
answering their phones. They're going to
stop texting and we need to have strong
evidence so that these technologies remain
viable and deliver real value.!